[{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":42178,"timeElapsed":336221},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":21862,"timeElapsed":358098},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980587175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":34836,"timeElapsed":392943},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":22959,"timeElapsed":415919},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13988,"timeElapsed":429916},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980632291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":8136,"timeElapsed":438059},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644229,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":11931,"timeElapsed":449997},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":46731,"timeElapsed":496736},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980711133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":20148,"timeElapsed":516901},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980785793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":70768,"timeElapsed":591560},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980819992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":34192,"timeElapsed":625760},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980850021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":30025,"timeElapsed":655789},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980871731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":21701,"timeElapsed":677499},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980900643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":28891,"timeElapsed":706410},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980954724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":54069,"timeElapsed":760492},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980958678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3940,"timeElapsed":764446},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980966694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":8002,"timeElapsed":772462},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980971694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4987,"timeElapsed":777462},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981000893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":27368,"timeElapsed":806661},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981018139,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":17234,"timeElapsed":823907},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981040000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":21851,"timeElapsed":845767},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981080327,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":40318,"timeElapsed":886095},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981090540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10197,"timeElapsed":896308},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981094099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3553,"timeElapsed":899867},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981101864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7756,"timeElapsed":907632},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981122294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":20420,"timeElapsed":928062},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981141674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":19376,"timeElapsed":947442},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981311905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":168415,"timeElapsed":1117671},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981314880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2967,"timeElapsed":1120648},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981365796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":50898,"timeElapsed":1171564},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981397702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":31896,"timeElapsed":1203469},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981404077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6353,"timeElapsed":1209845},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981427668,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":23579,"timeElapsed":1233435},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981432068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4388,"timeElapsed":1237836},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981435933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3863,"timeElapsed":1241701},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981458828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":22888,"timeElapsed":1264596},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981462071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3226,"timeElapsed":1267839},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981495955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":31982,"timeElapsed":1301723},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981510297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14332,"timeElapsed":1316065},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981538623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":28320,"timeElapsed":1344391},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981543003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4361,"timeElapsed":1348771},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981546345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3335,"timeElapsed":1352112},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981572818,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":26452,"timeElapsed":1378586},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981576882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4047,"timeElapsed":1382650},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981580907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4018,"timeElapsed":1386675},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981587696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6776,"timeElapsed":1393464},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981591537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3837,"timeElapsed":1397305},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981649804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":56646,"timeElapsed":1455571},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981656005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":6182,"timeElapsed":1461773},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981661085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5056,"timeElapsed":1466853},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981665390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4300,"timeElapsed":1471158},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981669158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3751,"timeElapsed":1474926},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981672523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3355,"timeElapsed":1478291},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981675439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2904,"timeElapsed":1481207},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981680603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":5145,"timeElapsed":1486371},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981685280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4673,"timeElapsed":1491048},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981726303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":39312,"timeElapsed":1532070},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981730725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4401,"timeElapsed":1536493},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981735086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4348,"timeElapsed":1540853},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981738454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3354,"timeElapsed":1544222},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981744799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6337,"timeElapsed":1550567},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981748286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3476,"timeElapsed":1554054},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981751190,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2888,"timeElapsed":1556957},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981757213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6014,"timeElapsed":1562981},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981761105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3887,"timeElapsed":1566873},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981798681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":34988,"timeElapsed":1604446},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981803563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4873,"timeElapsed":1609331},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981819778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":16213,"timeElapsed":1625546},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981821895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2094,"timeElapsed":1627662},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981824954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3054,"timeElapsed":1630722},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981828382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3414,"timeElapsed":1634150},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981832962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4556,"timeElapsed":1638729},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981837441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4472,"timeElapsed":1643209},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981840428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2977,"timeElapsed":1646196},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981895948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":53979,"timeElapsed":1701716},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981899655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3682,"timeElapsed":1705423},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981902859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3189,"timeElapsed":1708627},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981905127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2264,"timeElapsed":1710895},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981908713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3573,"timeElapsed":1714481},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981911162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2441,"timeElapsed":1716929},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981914138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2970,"timeElapsed":1719906},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981918319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4162,"timeElapsed":1724086},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981921158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2830,"timeElapsed":1726926},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981948175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":24908,"timeElapsed":1753943},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981952569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4370,"timeElapsed":1758337},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981956395,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3813,"timeElapsed":1762161},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981958822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2421,"timeElapsed":1764590},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981962374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3542,"timeElapsed":1768142},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981965793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3407,"timeElapsed":1771561},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981968650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2840,"timeElapsed":1774417},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981972006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3348,"timeElapsed":1777774},{"subjectID":"25ayct4ldw","prolificID":"66c61757724d29c2c00376a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b253d866dab65bf943c6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981976289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4274,"timeElapsed":1782057}]